Ralph T. Walker Papers
Ralph T. Walker Papers
- Trinidad files
  - Caribbean Architect and Engineer, 2 folders (Box 28)
  - Correspondence, 2 folders (Box 28)
  - Correspondence, Jan-Aug 1942; 7 folders (Box 28)
  - Estimates of Costs (Box 28)
  - Foley (Box 28)
  - Job Meetings (Box 29)
  - Meetings - Reports and Minutes (Box 29)
  - Memoranda (Box 29)
  - Personal Correspondence (Box 29)
  - Progress Reports (Box 29)
  - War Department Correspondence (Box 29)
- International Union of Architects files
  - Athens, 1954 (Box 29)
  - Cairo, 1950 (Box 29)
  - Committees (Box 29)
  - Congress - Netherlands, 1955 (Box 29)
  - Congress - Moscow, 1957 (Box 29)
  - Delegate Reports (Box 29)
  - Diary (Box 29)
  - Economic and Social Council (Box 29)
  - Executive Committee Meetings, 5 folders (Box 29)
  - Expenses (Box 29)
  - Finances (Box 29)
  - General (Box 30)
  - Housing (Box 30)
  - Lausanne (Box 30)
  - Lisbon, 2 folders (Box 30)
  - Minutes and Bulletins (Box 30)
  - Miscellaneous (Box 30)
  - Morocco (Box 30)
  - National Architectural Organizations (Box 30)
  - Paris, 5 folders (Box 30)
  - Poland (Box 30)
  - Publications (Box 30)
  - Rome (Box 30)
  - Sections (Box 30)
  - Statesmanship (Box 31)
  - Sweden (Box 31)
  - Translations (Box 31)
  - Venice (Box 31)
  - World Congress for Peace (Box 31)
  - Booklets and Notebooks, 11 volumes (Box 31)
- Literature
  - Biography (Box 31)
  - Criticism - General (Box 31)
  - Criticism - Saturday Review, 2 folders (Box 31)
  - French Literature, 2 folders (Box 31)
  - French Literature (Box 32)
  - Miscellaneous (Box 32)
  - Poetry
    - 18th Century (Box 32)
    - 19th Century, 6 folders (Box 32)
    - 20th Century, 2 folders (Box 32)
  - Prose (Box 32)
- T.S. Eliot
  - Criticism on Ezra Pound (Box 32)
  - Criticism on T.S. Eliot, 2 folders (Box 32)
  - Writings
    - Autographed Works and Letter (Box 32)
    - Journal Articles (Box 32)
    - Journal Articles, 3 folders (Box 33)
    - The Listener (Box 33)
    - Literary Criticism (Box 33)
    - Plays, 2 folders (Box 33)
    - Poetry, 2 folders (Box 33)
    - Social and Literary Criticism, 2 folders (Box 33)
    - Works in Foreign Languages, 2 folders (Box 33)
- Miscellaneous
  - Certificates and Awards (Oversize 5)
  - Framed Photographs and Certificates (Box 34)
  - Midtown Manhattan: Report to Groups Four and Five, New York City Savings Banks Study of Proposed Zoning Amendments (Voorhees, Walker, Foley & Smith), 1944; spiral-bound presentation book in clamshell case (Oversize 13)
  - Shop Drawings - Philadelphia Auditorium (1 bound stack) (Oversize 5)